<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello, I&#39;m Julien. on ʕ•ᴥ•ʔ</title>
    <link>https://scroix.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hello, I&#39;m Julien. on ʕ•ᴥ•ʔ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Oct 1988 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scroix.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://scroix.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scroix.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>🏡 Habitat Abstraction Layer (2017 - 2020) A dynamic control system for Featherston House.
    An architecturally award winning house designed by prominent Australian Robin Boyd in the late 1960s.
  An intuitive climate control system that forecasts the weather, and then prepares the building for various conditions based on modern adaptive comfort modelling, similar to ASHRAE-55 and EN-15251.
  Comprising of over a dozen temperature and humidity sensors, plus solar and wind read across a series of ADAM-6017s, scraped forecast data, and then a series of ADAM-6060s, plus some vendor-specific controllers for HVAC, Solar shades, Destratification fans etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work</title>
      <link>https://scroix.github.io/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scroix.github.io/work/</guid>
      <description>Museums Victoria (2016 - 2019) Comprising of Melbourne Museum (with Bunjilaka), Scienceworks, the Immigration Museum, and the Royal Exhibition Building, and hosting two million visitors annually. Museums Victoria is the largest museums organisation in Australasia.
Nodel Project I worked primary on the integration of hardware, and development of new Python 🐍 &amp;ldquo;recipes&amp;rdquo; as part of a project to replace a legacy software system responsible for control, monitoring and scheduling for around 400 exhibits (that&amp;rsquo;s ~2000 pieces of networked audio-visual equipment) across all venues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>https://scroix.github.io/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 18:27:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scroix.github.io/education/</guid>
      <description>RMIT University Bachelor of Software Engineering (B.SE) 2014 - 2019 3.5 GPA  A couple of neat projects completed during this degree&amp;hellip;
 A simple turn-based strategy game employing common design patterns (☕). A algorithm oriented maze generator (and solver!) (☕). A solution to OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s FrozenLake-v0 (🐍) An AI-bot for a game of Connect 4 (🐍) A group of three.js generated turtles calmly swimming in a pond.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>